<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight for the Future</title>
    <description>Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet&#39;s transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.</description>
    <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Yahoo let the NSA read your email before you even opened it.</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Yahoo was just &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-yahoo-nsa-exclusive-idUSKCN1241YT&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;revealed&lt;/a&gt; to be the very first US internet company to build a program, at the request of US Intelligence Services, to search every single incoming message of every single user in real time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let me say that again. Every. Single. Incoming. Message. Every user.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an absolutely unprecedented privacy violation. Surveillance experts and former government officials are saying they have never seen such a broad demand for real-time digital surveillance, nevermind one that calls for the creation of a new computer program. This program, essentially a wire-tap on the web, is beyond the scope of any of the already overreaching surveillance laws currently on the books. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The order issued to Yahoo appears to be unprecedented and unconstitutional. The government appears to have compelled Yahoo to conduct precisely the type of general, suspicionless search that the Fourth Amendment was intended to prohibit,” said ACLU Staff Attorney Patrick Toomey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication giants Microsoft, Twitter, Google, Facebook, and Apple have all rushed to &lt;a href=&quot;https://theintercept.com/2016/10/04/delete-your-yahoo-account/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;put out statements&lt;/a&gt; assuring users that they had not received or complied with similar directives, some going so far as to say that if they had they would challenge it in court. Apple pointed to a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/privacy/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;statement &lt;/a&gt;by CEO Tim Cook, which reads, “I want to be absolutely clear that we have never worked with any government agency from any country to create a backdoor in any of our products or services. We have also never allowed access to our servers. And we never will.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Yahoo &lt;a href=&quot;https://theintercept.com/2016/10/05/yahoo-offers-non-denial-denial-of-bombshell-spy-report/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;issued a statement &lt;/a&gt;that does not outright deny that the program existed, nor address the myriad of privacy and security concerns that have been raised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even former Yahoo Chief Information Security Officer, Alex Stamos, is appalled by the program. When he found out about it in 2015 he immediately resigned his position, telling coworkers that he had been excluded from the decision to implement the program. He also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2016/oct/04/yahoo-secret-email-program-nsa-fbi&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;cited flaws&lt;/a&gt; that seriously endangered the security of user data and left the program vulnerable to hackers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;4198&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2551&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/fd0710418582a5572e77f494a41eab18/tumblr_inline_oemx6r3hqy1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4198&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2551&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Yahoo is a sinking ship.&lt;/b&gt; This is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2016/09/29/technology/daily-report-latest-hack-shows-yahoos-weak-security-history.html?rref=collection%2Ftimestopic%2FYahoo!%20Inc.&amp;amp;action=click&amp;amp;contentCollection=business&amp;amp;region=stream&amp;amp;module=stream_unit&amp;amp;version=latest&amp;amp;contentPlacement=2&amp;amp;pgtype=collection&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;not the first &lt;/a&gt;security problem Yahoo has struggled with. Just last month it was revealed that over 500 million (and possibly &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/yahoo-insider-hacking-2016-9&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;many many millions more&lt;/a&gt;) Yahoo user accounts were compromised by “state sponsored actors.” This hack was almost certainly a result of Yahoo &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2016/09/29/technology/yahoo-data-breach-hacking.html?_r=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;consistently refusing&lt;/a&gt; to invest in the necessary and standard security practices adopted by their competitors after a massive hack six years ago, to which Yahoo also fell victim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And their security is not going to get any better. Yahoo was recently &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2016/07/25/business/yahoo-sale.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sold&lt;/a&gt; to Verizon for 4.8 billion dollars. Telecom companies including Verizon have been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/nsa-tracking-cellphone-locations-worldwide-snowden-documents-show/2013/12/04/5492873a-5cf2-11e3-bc56-c6ca94801fac_story.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;colluding&lt;/a&gt; with the NSA for years to gather information on billions of people worldwide, as Edward Snowden’s 2013 revelations have shown. Beyond handing your data to a prying NSA, Verizon also &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-lazarus-20140425-column.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;notoriously created&lt;/a&gt; an innovative way to track your online habits on both your phone and on your non-Verizon devices like personal laptops. They then sell your information to marketers. The Verizon-Yahoo merger is going to compound the security issues these two companies have created, resulting in a service where your communication becomes nothing more than a piece of data to be rifled through by the government and sold to the highest bidder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;You deserve to have the safety and privacy you expect. It’s time to dump Yahoo.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://help.yahoo.com/kb/SLN2044.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here’s how to delete your Yahoo account.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:46:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-06-yahoo-let-the-nsa-read-your-email-before-you-even/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-06-yahoo-let-the-nsa-read-your-email-before-you-even/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anti-Flag to headline free “Rock Against the TPP” concert in Pittsburgh as part of nationwide tour protesting Trans-Pacific Partnership</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/669e83a68d95c6da5a94a906eb1d87a4/tumblr_inline_oekg3nk8821ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Media Advisory for Thursday, November 3rd, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PITTSBURGH, PA––Popular Pittsburgh-based punk band Anti-Flag will headline a free concert at Mr Smalls Theater on Thursday, November 3rd, as part of the nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” tour, which features high profile musicians and celebrities sounding the alarm about the dangers of the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular corporate deal that has been a contentious issue this election year. The show runs from 6pm - 11pm and will also feature legendary Pittsburgh labor singer Anne Feeney, buzzworthy bi-lingual rockers Downtown Boys, plus Taina Asili, Evan Greer, Ryan Harvey, and Son of Nun, as well as speakers from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more details and a full lineup here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/pittsburgh-pa&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/pittsburgh-pa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/151282317108/photos-video-rock-against-the-tpp-tour-draws&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS &amp;amp; VIDEO from previous stops here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anti-Flag are one of the most popular musical acts to emerge from Pittsburgh, and tour extensively performing politically charged punk rock that’s half circle pit, half picket line. The band issued the following statement ahead of the November 3rd concert: &amp;ldquo;The Rock Against The TPP shows that we have played across the US and Canada were so amazing that we had to curate one in our beloved hometown of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania - Pittsburgh, an international epicenter of the labor movement  - a city where union loyalty and the fight for human rights courses through the veins of its citizens to this very day. The Rock Against The TPP shows are beyond educational, they&amp;rsquo;re inspirational. They are a true testament to music&amp;rsquo;s ability to bring people together and create positive change; a rally to energize us all to continue to fight against The TPP and all of the ills it will bring to the world.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Trans-Pacific Partnership is not about ‘free trade,’ it’s about corruption,” said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, “we’re harnessing the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about this corporate power grab and stop it in its tracks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by digital rights group Fight for the Future in partnership with legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave) and riot-folk singer Ryan Harvey’s record label Firebrand Records, previous stops on the Rock Against the TPP tour have featured high-profile participants including actress Evangeline Lilly, hip hop icon Talib Kweli, comedian Hari Kondabolu, Dead Kennedys singer Jello Biafra, legendary punk band Anti-Flag, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation Chumbawamba, and ANTI records songwriter Jolie Holland. The roadshow has already drawn &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;large crowds&lt;/a&gt; in Denver, San Diego, Seattle, Portland, San Francisco, and Toronto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers. The Pittsburgh stop is also backed by the Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, PA Fair Trade Coalition, and Fight Back Pittsburgh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with artists or organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 04:40:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-05-anti-flag-to-headline-free-rock-against-the-tpp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-05-anti-flag-to-headline-free-rock-against-the-tpp/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS &amp; VIDEO: Rock Against the TPP tour draws large crowds across the U.S. to protest Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DiZXiwbzSDTA&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iZXiwbzSDTA?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rock Against the TPP tour has drawn large crowds across the U.S., making it the biggest nationwide ground mobilization against the Trans-Pacific Partnership deal to date. These photos and videos are available for use by press. Contact: press@fightforthefuture.org with inquiries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/669e83a68d95c6da5a94a906eb1d87a4/tumblr_inline_oegsk7MlN51ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portland, OR. Photo credit: Gaetano Vacarro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/352a026f1fcfcf171441800c6fea4f9a/tumblr_inline_oegsxho7sF1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denver, CO. Photo credit: Evan Greer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/3b2d5572272d5869ae73bccb405eb90c/tumblr_inline_oegsyeREiY1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Francisco, CA. Photo Credit: Peter Booth Lee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;853&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/971aa7f33ed727fe20195e279289d7e6/tumblr_inline_oegszdrE4J1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;853&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talib Kweli in Seattle. Photo Credit: Rick Barry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/724abea530f91583e5487a3e9858a9ba/tumblr_inline_oegt0rMkA51ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denver, CO. Photo credit: Evan Greer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1063&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1600&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/671789288e477067799a97c0be6b2145/tumblr_inline_oegt36sBqH1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1063&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1600&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Morello finale in Denver. Photo: Courtesy FFTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;854&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/2284013f830d11c06a36c1b77db4cbdb/tumblr_inline_oegt4in14E1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;854&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seattle, WA. Photo: Rick Barry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/968ac9c1a46408c74faf2cf72885548d/tumblr_inline_oegt5kautv1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evangeline Lilly at rally in Denver. Photo: Evan Greer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VIDEOS AVAILABLE FOR PRESS TO EMBED:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D9ugC4NG1Zoc&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9ugC4NG1Zoc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FkA9nIeVvcMw%3Flist%3DPL_4XTYYQE31Bh8xjNrtJMokVBJPuddISh&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 05:33:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-03-photos-video-rock-against-the-tpp-tour-draws/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-03-photos-video-rock-against-the-tpp-tour-draws/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FIRST EVER TEXT-TO-REGISTER VOTING CHAT BOT DEBUTS IN TIME FOR NATIONAL VOTER REGISTRATION DAY</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Media Contact:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jon Reinish, 202-999-0461 JReinish@skdknick.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;HelloVote Revolutionizes Voter Registration, Brings Millions of Tough-to-Reach Millennials, Minority Voters into the Political Process&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New York, New York  (September 21, 2016)&lt;/b&gt; – HelloVote, a first-of-its-kind voter registration chat bot that allows voters to register using SMS text or Facebook Messenger, debuts in the heat of the 2016 Presidential election - just in time for National Voter Registration Day and state-level registration deadlines. HelloVote has the potential to transform voter participation by bringing registration firmly into the digital era. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Census data reveals that as a whole 33% of eligible voters are not registered - and that two of this election cycle’s most valued groups, Latino voters and voters 18-24, are vastly under-registered by about 40%. Nearly 30% of self described liberals are not registered. Only about 50% of voters without a college degree are registered; and the less money you earn the more likely you are rely on your phone for internet access. HelloVote takes the registration process right to the voter – instead of the other way around, and may make millennials, immigrants and communities of color the decisive game changers in this closely contested election up and down the ballot by leveraging up to date technology and social media.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voters can go to hello.vote, text 384-387 on their mobile device, or (go to m.me/hellovote in Facebook messenger) to prompt the registration process. Text messaging is quickly becoming the country’s preferred way of communicating, with a 98% open rate and an average 90 second response time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using HelloVote, the entire registration process takes under one minute – a key factor when nearly 20% of respondents tell Pew that registration takes too much time. The effort is being magnified through a diverse range of national and regional partners including MTV, SEIU CA, Genius, Twilio, HeadCount, General Assembly, Auttomatic (makers of WordPress), Mijente, the Shade Room, Latino Victory Project, TurboVote, Care2, West Elm, the Asian American Resource Center, Korean Resource Center, Presente.org, Daily Kos, the Bus Federation, 18 Million Rising, and New American Leaders Project as well as celebrity supporters. New partnerships will be announced on a rolling basis over the next several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A full ninety-six percent of Americans have a mobile phone and now they can use it to register to vote – bringing voter registration to any smartphone or flip phone holder and transforming an archaic process,” said Tiffiniy Cheng, an expert in voter technology who is one of the five co-founders of HelloVote. “This election is probably the most-discussed in our lifetime, and HelloVote aims to turn talkers into voters. The reality is that today we work, play and shop on our phones. HelloVote is a revolution in democracy making and bringing voter registration out of the dark ages and into the current cycle, hopefully making the difference for people who may never have registered but can now by text.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HelloVote’s technology works in compliance with voter registration regulation in all 50 states. Americans will be able to text-to-register up until their state’s registration deadlines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Democracy depends on participation, and technology has the power to significantly reduce barriers that have traditionally stopped people from voting,&amp;rdquo; said Twilio Vice President of Product Management, Patrick Malatack. &amp;ldquo;HelloVote is a great example of how communications can make any user experience more efficient. By making it easier for people to sign up from anywhere, on any mobile phone with no Internet required - HelloVote has streamlined the voter registration process. We are excited to see more people getting out and voting in 2016 as a result of this valuable service.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Whether it&amp;rsquo;s social media, video, podcasts, or simply news articles we&amp;rsquo;re bookmarking on our phones, information about this election has been omnipresent, both easy to access and interact with,&amp;rdquo; said Nat Guevara, head of communications for Genius. &amp;ldquo;Voter registration should be just as ubiquitous, convenient, and available to as many communities as possible. We&amp;rsquo;re partnering with HelloVote to make the registration process less daunting so that our audience can prioritize what&amp;rsquo;s actually important: informing themselves on the issues they care about and making it out to the polls.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re very excited to partner with Hello Vote on this cutting edge platform which uses text messaging and Facebook to register Latinos to vote,&amp;rdquo; said Cesar J. Blanco, Interim Director for Latino Victory Project. &amp;ldquo;The stakes are too high to sit this election out. Now more than ever, it&amp;rsquo;s paramount that organizations leverage new and exciting technology to find potential voters where they&amp;rsquo;re at, and get them to vote. This program represents the future of voter registration, and Latino Victory Project is ready to mobilize our communities around our issues and priorities.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“General Assembly is a global community of learners 350,000 strong, and our students and alumni take part in our programs both on campus and online, said Liz Simon, Vice President of Legal and External Affairs at General Assembly. “Having the option to get registered via text – and get their friends registered – is the best way to engage our community here in the States. We’re excited that members of the GA network, no matter where they are or what their party affiliation, have this user-friendly way to get involved in the political process.&amp;ldquo; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;This is the kind of technology that truly can change the game. HelloVote makes voter registration as easy as sending a few texts, literally,&amp;rdquo; said Andy Bernstein, executive director, HeadCount. “HeadCount will be rolling HelloVote on National Voter Registration Day and organizing 200+ musicians to post on social media about it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;For the past several cycles, experts have been stumped on how to register Latino voters who remain under-activated and participate at lower levels than other demographic groups,” said Javier Palomarez, President and CEO of the U.S. Hispanic Chamber of Commerce. “Placing technology right in the hands of the voter is one solution we believe in and that&amp;rsquo;s why we look forward to bringing as many Latino voters into the political process as possible in partnership with HelloVote.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our goal is to get as many Care2 members registered to vote as possible, and Hello!Vote is making that so much easier than any other tool we’ve found, said Emily Logan, Director of Acquisition and Retention at Care2. “That ease of use is so important to make sure the barriers for registration are low and that everyone is able to have their voice heard through voting.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “We are employing every tool available to engage the people who’s lives have been hurt and whose votes have been previously suppressed to make sure that our communities move forward, not backwards, this election season,” said Marisa Franco, director of Mijente. “HelloVote will be a crucial addition to flex the power of the 200,000 new potential voters in the Phoenix area who have come of age since 2012.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Neighborhood by neighborhood, and cell phone by cell phone, we’ll fight for more Latinx community participation in voting. HelloVote raises the voices of everyday folks who would otherwise be discouraged from actively participating in our democracy,” said Statement from Matt Nelson, Executive Director, Presente.org. This kind of innovation moves us toward a more just, more democratic country that includes ALL of us—especially our families, friends, and neighbors who are heavily impacted by racial, economic, and gender injustice.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is critical for democracy to get everyone involved in the upcoming election,” said Peter Slutsky of Automattic, the parent company of WordPress.com. We are thrilled to work with HelloVote to help make it as easy as possible for U.S. voters to register and make their voices heard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; About HelloVote&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HelloVote is the first chatbot-based tool that allows voters to register over text message or Facebook Messenger in under one minute. HelloVote dramatically improves the user experience of civic participation for millions of mobile-first Americans in collaboration with partners nationwide. Co-created by Tiffiniy Cheng, Jeff Lyon, Josh Levinger, Holmes Wilson, and Elana Berkowitz, HelloVote is a non-partisan 501c3 project of Fight for the Future and the Fight for the Future Education Fund. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:30:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-23-first-ever-text-to-register-voting-chat-bot-debuts/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-23-first-ever-text-to-register-voting-chat-bot-debuts/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Prison disciplinary board decides to punish Chelsea Manning with solitary confinement for charges related to suicide attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/d28dd008264e4d389a332ff9d6e47b0a/tumblr_inline_odyem99UoA1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: September 23, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEAVENWORTH, KS––A prison disciplinary board has decided to punish imprisoned transparency advocate Chelsea Manning with 14 days of solitary confinement (with 7 days suspended) for&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150739860858/fight-for-the-future-releases-formal-charge-sheet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;charges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; directly related to her suicide attempt in July, and possession of an unmarked book in her cell. The decision is the latest example of the U.S. government’s campaign of harassment and mistreatment of Chelsea, who has been incarcerated in all male military facilities for 6 years.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a detailed summary of the charges Chelsea faced &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150739860858/fight-for-the-future-releases-formal-charge-sheet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chelsea Manning released the following statement to supporters:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My three member disciplinary board took place today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I presented evidence and was allowed to question witnesses through the board president. The hearing lasted four hours. There was a break for lunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I waited nervously for the board to vote. I received the decision after 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was acquitted of the &amp;ldquo;Resisting The Force Cell Move Team&amp;rdquo; charge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was found guilty of the &amp;ldquo;Conduct Which Threatens&amp;rdquo; charge. This charge was for the suicide attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was found guilty of the &amp;ldquo;Prohibited Property&amp;rdquo; charge, which was for an unmarked copy of &amp;ldquo;Hacker, Hoaxer, Whistleblower, Spy,&amp;rdquo; by Gabriella Coleman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My punishment is 14 days in solitary confinement. 7 of those days are &amp;ldquo;suspended.&amp;rdquo; If I get in trouble in the next six months, those seven days will come back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term for this status is &amp;ldquo;disciplinary segregation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no set date set for this to start. After I receive the formal board results in writing, I have 15 days to appeal. I expect to get them in the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am feeling hurt. I am feeling lonely. I am embarrassed by the decision. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to explain it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am touched by your warm messages of love and support. This comforts me in my time of need.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, following a 5-day &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150374089598/breaking-chelsea-manning-ends-hunger-strike-after&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;hunger strike&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and a flurry of public protest, the government finally agreed to provide Chelsea with some of the health care that she needs. Despite the good news related to medical treatment, Chelsea will now be punished with solitary confinement, which the United Nations has &lt;a href=&quot;http://solitarywatch.com/2015/07/24/un-human-rights-experts-again-push-for-access-to-u-s-prisons-call-for-solitary-confinement-reform/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;condemned&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; as a form of torture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The July incident where Chelsea attempted to take her own life followed years of the government systematically denying her access to medically recommended treatment for gender dysphoria, and &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/126526891688/breaking-whistleblower-chelsea-manning-faces&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;previous threats&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;of solitary confinement following minor prison “infractions,” including possession of mislabeled general research materials that Chelsea used for article writing and an expired tube of toothpaste.	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After she receives written notification of her solitary confinement sentence, Chelsea has 15 days to appeal the disciplinary board’s decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the digital rights group that has been supporting Chelsea, is encouraging all supporters of human rights to sign the petition at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeChelsea.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;calling for the U.S. government to drop these unjust charges. Celebrities including &lt;b&gt;Michael Stipe&lt;/b&gt; of REM, Pentagon Papers whistleblower &lt;b&gt;Daniel Ellsberg&lt;/b&gt;, and &lt;b&gt;Thurston Moore&lt;/b&gt; of Sonic Youth, have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC23i3ArkcoLSIJ8C02CjX7A&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;uploaded videos&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; speaking out on Chelsea’s behalf and asking fans to sign the petition. The group plans to keep supporters updated on Chelsea’s situation, and ways to take action to support her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: for verification purposes, see &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/chasestrangio/status/779275451642503168&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; from Chelsea Manning’s attorney at the ACLU, Chase Strangio.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;202&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;559&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/07f73141c9ae2e6882c8941beb82020e/tumblr_inline_odyfb3erSj1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;202&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;559&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 07:01:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-23-breaking-prison-disciplinary-board-decides-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-23-breaking-prison-disciplinary-board-decides-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future Releases Formal Charge Sheet And Other Documents Ahead of Chelsea Manning Disciplinary Board</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/d28dd008264e4d389a332ff9d6e47b0a/tumblr_inline_odvezoBNo71ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Manning faces an administrative disciplinary board tomorrow that may punish her for charges directly related to her July suicide attempt. This board is happening even though it was the government’s own mistreatment of Chelsea that drove her to attempt to take her own life earlier this year.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The process of preparing for the board has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/sep/20/chelsea-manning-gender-surgery-suicide-attempt-punishment&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;very emotional and traumatizing for Chelsea&lt;/a&gt;. It requires her to continually relive the painful experience over and over again. Chelsea must prepare her defense completely on her own, and will appear in front of the three person panel alone. She is not permitted to consult with or have an attorney or other advocate present during the hearing. The hearing itself could last for hours and there will be no transcript or account of the proceedings available to the public beyond what Chelsea herself is able to convey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Manning ended her hunger strike last week after the U.S. military agreed to move forward with some recommended treatment for her gender dysphoria. However, she found out the next day, when she was given a second, more detailed charge sheet, that the Army is continuing to threaten Chelsea with solitary confinement for charges directly related to her attempt to take her own life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news that she will be meeting with a surgeon, and may hopefully receive some of the currently withheld medical treatment for her gender dysphoria, was a huge relief, but that relief has been largely overshadowed by the prospect of solitary confinement. Solitary confinement, because of it’s harmful effects on those subject to it, has been &lt;a href=&quot;http://solitarywatch.com/2015/07/24/un-human-rights-experts-again-push-for-access-to-u-s-prisons-call-for-solitary-confinement-reform/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;defined by the UN as a form of torture&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is making some of the documents from Chelsea’s case available to help better explain what is happening to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These documents provide greater context around the charges. These kinds of minor infractions, in the larger context of what Chelsea is going through right now, is a perfect example of the &amp;ldquo;high tech bullying&amp;rdquo; that she first brought to light when she went on her hunger strike on September 9, 2016. Chelsea describes high tech bullying as “the constant, deliberate and overzealous administrative scrutiny by prison and military officials.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bottom line is that Chelsea could be in solitary by the end of the day tomorrow. &amp;ldquo;They could start punishing her right away,” explains Chase Strangio, her attorney at the ACLU. “Last time, she was able to call afterwards, and the punishment did not start immediately, but we were concerned then that it might have, and we are concerned now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Documents provided today for reference:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150729898078/chelsea-mannings-formal-charge-sheet-related-to&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Formal Charge Sheet&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0BzTpgEwjZfLIalgweEFYSHlnWWM/view?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;) (Dictated over the phone because the page was missing upon arrival to Chelsea’s counsel).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0BzTpgEwjZfLIRFNybVktTVpsT0k/view?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Accompanying documents to the Formal Charge Shee&lt;/a&gt;t&lt;br/&gt;a) Inmate Disciplinary Reports (pages 2-5)&lt;br/&gt;b) Discipline and Adjustment Board Notification (page 1)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://arba.army.pentagon.mil/documents/army%20corrections%20command/Institutional%20Offense%20Policy.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Policy Letter 16&lt;/a&gt; (Here’s an &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0BzTpgEwjZfLId2diMWQyRTRFSTg/view?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;OCR’d PDF&lt;/a&gt; of it) - which is referenced repeatedly in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150729898078/chelsea-mannings-formal-charge-sheet-related-to&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Formal Charge Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea sent an envelope of documents, including the &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150729898078/chelsea-mannings-formal-charge-sheet-related-to&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Formal Charge Sheet&lt;/a&gt; (the most important document, as far as Chelsea was concerned) to her attorney, Chase Strangio. One document was inadvertently left out, and so Chelsea dictated it to her support network over the phone last night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Formal Charge Sheet, contains three charges: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;1. Resisting the Force Cell Move Team &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This charge stems from the “force cell team” being activated. They were called to respond to her suicide attempt, though there were no obstructions to the door and Chelsea was unconscious and unable to resist when they arrived. The charge sheet itself specifies on page 5 that &amp;ldquo;Inmate Manning did not resist the force cell move team.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;2. Conduct Which Threatens&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This charge amounts to disturbing the orderly running of the facility. Chelsea did not ever engage in “threatening behavior,” the prison interprets “conduct that threatens” broadly to encompass any activity that disrupts the normal routine and charging Chelsea because her suicide attempted allegedly did that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;3. Prohibited Property&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 6th, Gabriella Coleman&amp;rsquo;s book &amp;ldquo;Hacker, Hoaxer, Whistleblower, Spy&amp;rdquo; was found in Chelsea’s cell, allegedly not properly marked with Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s name and inmate number on the inside cover. (A new regulation, that appears to have been crafted in response to Chelsea’s confiscated books/expired toothpaste incident from last summer.) In fact, this book was one of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dailydot.com/layer8/books-they-wont-let-chelsea-manning-read/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;books confiscated from Chelsea’s cell last summer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of thousands of people spoke out in support of Chelsea, and now, as a result, the government is finally agreeing to move forward with some of her longstanding medical treatment needs. It is difficult trust even this assurance, though, given that they are on the one hand recognizes that she has an urgent need for treatment but on the other punishing her for the consequences of having had that treatment denied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For inquiries, contact: Evan Greer, Fight for the Future, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpts from &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0BzTpgEwjZfLId2diMWQyRTRFSTg/view?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Policy Letter 16&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) RESISTING THE FORCE CELL MOVE TEAM CAT IV OR V&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the &amp;ldquo;force cell team to be called to the cell&amp;rdquo; [Section &amp;ldquo;oo&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete text of description from the prison rules:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Section oo. Resisting Forced Cell Moves (Category IV or V offense). Any action taken to impede, resist, or interfere with the actions of forced cell move teams, including, but not limited to, trying to keep the cell door closed, throwing objects at the Force Cell Move Team (FCMT) or attempting to grab team members while in the performance of their duties. &lt;b&gt;Any action taken that causes the FCMT to be activated, even if it is not used is a category IV offense.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;//Despite the misleading charge name, we have bolded the sentence that allows the prison to punish Chelsea for the team being called at all &amp;ndash; a perfect example of the prison making the rules apply whenever they see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;2) PROHIBITED PROPERTY III&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prohibited use of property [Section &amp;ldquo;ii&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete text of description from the prison rules:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Section ii. Prohibited Property (Category III offense). Anything not specifically authorized by proper authority to be in a prisoner&amp;rsquo;s possession is prohibited. Prisoners must obtain and keep written permission from the Facility Commander, or authorized representative, to possess any item not authorized by facility policy or staff. Any item not specifically authorized and found in a prisoner&amp;rsquo;s possession will be considered prohibited property. Possession of property obtained from trash receptacles, or that which was discarded in any other way by other prisoners or staff is prohibited. Property that has been altered from its original form without facility authorization will be considered prohibited property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note that there is nothing stated about books needing to be labeled on the inside cover. These were&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;general research reference materials that Chelsea uses for article writing. These materials were never returned to her. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;3) CONDUCT WHICH THREATENS IV&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;This accuses her of conduct which threatens [Section &amp;ldquo;m&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete text of description from the prison rules:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Section m. Conduct Which Threatens (Category IV offense). Any conduct which interferes with the orderly running, safety, good order and discipline, or security the facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Somehow she is being charged with threatening the “safety&amp;quot; of the facility. As if her actions, alone in her cell to herself, could put the prison facility at risk.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relevant Press Releases: 	 	&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Manning Faces New Charges, Indefinite Solitary Confinement Related to Suicide Attempt - Government Continues to Deny Manning Access to Health Care&lt;br/&gt;ACLU Press Release, July 28, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/news/chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite-solitary-confinement-related-suicide-attempt&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.aclu.org/news/chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite-solitary-confinement-related-suicide-attempt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Manning begins hunger strike protest&lt;br/&gt;Chelsea Manning Support Network Press Release, September 9, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chelseamanning.org/featured/chelsea-manning-begins-hunger-strike-protest&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.chelseamanning.org/featured/chelsea-manning-begins-hunger-strike-protest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Manning ends hunger strike after Army agrees to provide her with gender reassignment surgery - Still faces indefinite solitary confinement for suicide attempt&lt;br/&gt;Fight for the Future Press Release, September 13, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-13-breaking-chelsea-manning-ends-hunger-strike-after/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-13-breaking-chelsea-manning-ends-hunger-strike-after/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 16:11:07 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-21-fight-for-the-future-releases-formal-charge-sheet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-21-fight-for-the-future-releases-formal-charge-sheet/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning’s formal charge sheet related to July suicide attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The text below appears on a “Formal Charge Sheet” provided to Chelsea Manning by U.S. Army Officials. It was dictated in full over the phone to a supporter. Inquiries, contact: press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/i&gt;10-August-16&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FORMAL CHARGE SHEET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charge: Resisting the FCMT (Causing the FCMT to be activated)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Category: ACC(pp) CAT IV&lt;br/&gt;Specification: On 5 July 2016, at approximately 01:00, you attempted to commit suicide, resulting in the activation of the Force Cell Move Team. You are violation of ACC Policy Letter 16 (link), any action taken that causes the FCMT to be activated, even if it is not used, is a Category IV offense. (CAT IV, V)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charge: Conduct which threatens&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Category: ACC(m) CAT IV&lt;br/&gt;Specification: On 5 July 2016 your intentional actions caused a double pals activation and cease movement order which interfered with the good order, safety, and running of the facility. You are in violation of ACC Policy Letter 16,  which prohibits any conduct which interferes with the orderly running, safety, good order and discipline, or security of the facility. (CAT IV)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charge: Prohibited Property&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Category: ACC(mm) CAT III&lt;br/&gt;Specification: On 5 July 2016, after an inspection of your cell, you were found to be in possession of an unmarked book. You are in violation of ACC Policy Letter 16 because anything not specifically authorized by proper authorities to be in a prisoner&amp;rsquo;s possession is prohibited. Prisoners must obtain and receive written permission from the Facility Commander, or authorized representative, to possess any item not authorized by facility policy or staff. Any item not specifically authorized and found in a prisoner&amp;rsquo;s possession will be considered prohibited property. Possession of prohibited property obtained from trash receptacles, or that which was discarded in any other way by prisoners and staff is prohibited. Property that has been altered from its original form without facility authorization will be considered prohibited property. (CAT III)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I acknowledge I have read, or have had read to me, the above charges on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHELSEA&amp;rsquo;S SIGNATURE                                           	 9 - Sep - 2016 (handwritten)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MCC Form 67-2 7-Sep-14&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 11:32:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-21-chelsea-mannings-formal-charge-sheet-related-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-21-chelsea-mannings-formal-charge-sheet-related-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Chelsea Manning ends hunger strike after Army agrees to provide her with gender reassignment surgery - Still faces indefinite solitary confinement for suicide attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F-P5hCu59yTs%3Flist%3DPLOoiLJ3t3QS3O0xoO0zZ1tBziwFxYwBAN&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/-P5hCu59yTs?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: September 13, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=mailto%3Apress%40balestramedia.com&amp;amp;t=ZWVlODQxZTI1ZGQ5YWYwYTc3N2RjMDk0MTNhMDcwMTQ4OTEyZjAzZCxWVzRrMDJnWg%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, Fight for the Future, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Supporters, including REM’s Michael Stipe and Daniel Ellsberg, launch new campaign at FreeChelsea.com demanding U.S. government drop charges stemming from suicide attempt&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEAVENWORTH, KS––Chelsea Manning has ended a hunger strike that she began five days ago, after the U.S. military has agreed to move forward with the recommended treatment for her gender dysphoria. However, the Army is continuing to threaten Chelsea with solitary confinement for charges directly related to her attempt to take her own life, even though it was the government’s own mistreatment of Chelsea that drove her to it.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supporters have launched a new effort at &lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeChelsea.com&lt;/a&gt; calling for the charges to be dropped. The site features a petition to the Secretary of the Army Eric Fanning as well as videos uploaded by supporters including Michael Stipe of R.E.M. and Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea alerted attorneys and supporters that she was ending the hunger strike after government officials showed her a memo stating that she will receive gender-reassignment surgery, under the DOD’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.defense.gov/Portals/1/features/2016/0616_policy/DoD-Instruction-1300.28.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;new policy&lt;/a&gt; affecting transgender service members. If this occurs, Manning will be the first transgender prisoner in the U.S. to receive this medically recommended treatment, setting a precedent that could benefit thousands of transgender prisoner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I am unendingly relieved that the military is finally doing the right thing. I applaud them for that. This is all that I wanted – for them to let me be me,” said Chelsea Manning in a statement to her attorneys. “But it is hard not to wonder why it has taken so long.  Also, why were such drastic measures needed? The surgery was recommended back in April 2016. The recommendations for my hair length were back in 2014. In any case, I hope this sets a precedent for the thousands of trans people behind me hoping they will be given the treatment they need.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is a relief to hear that the government has finally agreed to move forward with providing Chelsea with the health care that she is legally entitled to and is medically needed. We hope that they will act to provide this care without delay in order to ensure that her suffering does not continue,” said Chase Strangio, Chelsea’s attorney at the ACLU, “This medical care is absolutely vital for Chelsea. It was the government’s refusal to provide her with the necessary care that led her to attempt suicide earlier this year, and it was all the more troubling when she became subject to an investigation and possible punishment in connection with the suicide attempt. We hope that the government recognizes that charging Chelsea with the crime of being denied essential health care is outrageous and drops those charges.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hundreds of thousands of people spoke out in support of Chelsea, and now the government is finally agreeing to provide her with the healthcare treatment that she needs,” said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, the digital rights group behind FreeChelsea.com that has supported Chelsea over the last year, “but now that the Army is acknowledging Chelsea deserves this treatment, it’s even more outrageous that they’re still threatening her with solitary confinement for charges related to her own suicide attempt. It was the government’s refusal to grant Chelsea access to needed health care that led to her suicide attempt in the first place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea’s supporters plan to release more videos to raise awareness about the new petition at FreeChelsea.com in the coming days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FeYrhdUcfClE&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/eYrhdUcfClE?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 18:35:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-13-breaking-chelsea-manning-ends-hunger-strike-after/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-13-breaking-chelsea-manning-ends-hunger-strike-after/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” celebrity concert tour comes to Boston to protest Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D9ugC4NG1Zoc&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9ugC4NG1Zoc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Media Advisory for Friday, Oct 7 - Saturday, Sep 8, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Indie pop star Mirah, Ethiopian dance troupe Debo Band, best of Boston hip hop Foundation Movement and others to play free show on October 7th to raise awareness about the TPP corporate power grab&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOSTON, MA––On Friday, October 7th, as part of the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; tour, prominent musicians will lead the charge in mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP), the unpopular and anti-democratic deal that has been a contentious issue in the 2016 election. The tour, which is the largest mobilization against the TPP in U.S. history, comes to Spontaneous Celebrations in Jamaica Plain from 6pm - 10pm for a FREE concert featuring indie star &lt;b&gt;Mirah&lt;/b&gt;, beloved Ethiopian dance-pop troupe &lt;b&gt;Debo Band&lt;/b&gt;, renowned Boston hip hop duo &lt;b&gt;Foundation Movement&lt;/b&gt;, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See more details and a full lineup here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/boston-ma&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/boston-ma&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concert will be followed by a teach-in on “How to Fight the TPP” on Saturday, October 8th hosted by experts from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP. Time and location TBA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Trans-Pacific Partnership is not about ‘free trade,’ it’s about corruption,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, who is based in Jamaica Plain, and organizes the popular Break the Chains LGBTQ dance party series in Boston,&lt;/b&gt; “we’re harnessing the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about this corporate power grab and stop it in its tracks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by digital rights group Fight for the Future in partnership with legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave) and riot-folk singer &lt;b&gt;Ryan Harvey&lt;/b&gt;’s record label Firebrand Records, previous stops on the tour have featured high-profile participants including actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly,&lt;/b&gt; hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, Dead Kennedys singer &lt;b&gt;Jello Biafra&lt;/b&gt;, legendary punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Adult Swim comedian &lt;b&gt;Eric Andre&lt;/b&gt;, and ANTI records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The roadshow has already drawn &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;large crowds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in Denver, San Diego, Seattle, Portland, and San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety. The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers. Organizers plan to announce additional dates to the tour soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional performers at the October 7th event include afro-latin rock group Taina Asili y La Banda Rebelde and Firebrand Records artist Bell’s Roar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.xkq7oohiw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE PHOTOS AND VIDEO AVAILABLE FOR USE BY PRESS HERE.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with Artists or Organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 12:48:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-12-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-12-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: More than 1,000 attend Rock Against the TPP Concert in San Francisco</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/3b2d5572272d5869ae73bccb405eb90c/tumblr_inline_ode5p85Ytp1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, September 12, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Punk legend Jello Biafra, hip hop icons Dead Prez, Grammy winners La Santa Cecilia among participants in event protesting anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, CA––As the White House readies a final desperate push for the unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, large crowds turned out for the “Rock Against the TPP” tour stop in San Francisco over the weekend  as part of a nationwide tour of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests featuring high profile musicians and celebrities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of the SF event available for use by press here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/RLbo9&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/RLbo9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scroll down for a video clip from the event.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The packed San Francisco concert at Regency Ballroom featured performances by hip hop icons &lt;b&gt;Dead Prez&lt;/b&gt;, former Dead Kennedys singer &lt;b&gt;Jello Biafra&lt;/b&gt;, Grammy winners &lt;b&gt;La Santa Cecilia&lt;/b&gt;, and a wide range of other notable performers. The &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; tour has been drawing large crowds across the country all summer, with previous stops in Denver, San Diego, Seatte, and Portland amplified by well-known artists including &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, actress E&lt;b&gt;vangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt;, punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, comedians &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Eric Andre&lt;/b&gt;, and ANTI-records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS and VIDEO of previous events &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/150033228898/new-video-celebrities-comedians-musicians&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave) and &lt;b&gt;Ryan Harvey’&lt;/b&gt;s new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Trans-Pacific Partnership is not about ‘free trade,’ it’s about corruption,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, &lt;/b&gt;“we’re harnessing the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about this corporate power grab and stop it in its tracks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour stops next at a Canadian solidarity event in Toronto on September 16th featuring Anti-Flag and Rebel Diaz, and in Boston on Friday, October 7th featuring beloved indie-pop star Mirah and Ethiopian dance-pop troupe Debo Band. Additional tour dates are to be announced. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video clip from Dead Prez headlining set at Rock Against the TPP in San Francisco (professional video coming soon.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2Fzux0fhPhz6U&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zux0fhPhz6U?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:32:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-12-photos-more-than-1000-attend-rock-against-the/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-12-photos-more-than-1000-attend-rock-against-the/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning Begins Hunger Strike to Protest Bullying by Prison and US Government</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Immediate Release&lt;/b&gt;: September 9, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact&lt;/b&gt;: Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Fight for the Future has launched a petition supporting Chelsea in her hunger strike. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/petitions/stand-with-chelsea-manning-on-hunger-strike&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See the petition here. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, after years of requesting the care she needs for gender dysphoria, Chelsea Manning has released a statement about the start of her hunger strike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is demanding written assurances from the Army she will receive all of the medically prescribed recommendations for her gender dysphoria and that the “high tech bullying” will stop. “High tech bullying,” is what Chelsea describes as “the constant, deliberate and overzealous administrative scrutiny by prison and military officials.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following her sentencing, Chelsea has respectfully requested that the US Government give her treatment for her gender dysphoria. Over a year later, Chelsea filed a lawsuit in September of 2014, where she sued the government to get a battery of treatments. As a result, she began hormone therapy in February of 2015.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;However, the military has been making her cut her hair to the male length and grooming standards. As part of her treatment, her doctors recommended that she follow the military prison&amp;rsquo;s female hair grooming standards. In September of 2015 she amended her lawsuit, asking that the government allow her to grow her hair. The government’s response in December 2015 was &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo; The case is still active before a DC District court judge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Statement from Chelsea Manning:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need help. I am not getting any. I have asked for help time and time again for six years and through five separate confinement locations. My request has only been ignored, delayed, mocked, given trinkets and lip service by the prison, the military, and this administration.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need help. I needed help earlier this year. I was driven to suicide by the lack of care for my gender dysphoria that I have been desperate for. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get any. I still haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten any.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I needed help. Yet, instead I am now being punished for surviving my attempt. When I was a child, my father would beat me repeatedly for simply not being masculine enough. I was told to stop crying—to &amp;quot;suck it up.&amp;rdquo; But, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop crying. The pain just got worse and worse. Until finally, I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t take the pain anymore.&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I needed help, but no one came then. No one is coming now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Today, I have decided that I am no longer going to be bullied by this prison—or by anyone within the U.S. government. I have asked for nothing but the dignity and respect—that I once actually believed would be provided for—afforded to any living human being.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I do not believe that this should be dependent on any arbitrary factors—whether you are cisgender or transgender; service member or civilian, citizen or non-citizen. In response to virtually every request, I have been granted limited, if any, dignity and respect—just more pain and anguish.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am no longer asking. Now, I am demanding. As of 12:01 am Central Daylight Time on September 9, 2016, and until I am given minimum standards of dignity, respect, and humanity, I shall—refuse to voluntarily cut or shorten my hair in any way; consume any food or drink voluntarily, except for water and currently prescribed medications; and comply with all rules, regulations, laws, and orders that are not related to the two things I have mentioned.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;This is a peaceful act. I intend to keep it as peaceful and non-violent, on my end, as possible. Any physical harm that should come to me at the hands of military or civilian staff will be unnecessary and vindictive. I will not physically resist or in any way harm another person. I have also submitted a &amp;quot;do not resuscitate&amp;rdquo; letter that is effective immediately. This shall include any attempts to forcibly cut or shorten my hair or to forcibly feed me by any medical or pseudo-medical means.&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Until I am shown dignity and respect as a human again, I shall endure this pain before me. I am prepared for this mentally and emotionally. I expect that this ordeal will last for a long time. Quite possibly until my permanent incapacitation or death. I am ready for this.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need help. Please, give me help.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 16:21:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-09-chelsea-manning-begins-hunger-strike-to-protest/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-09-chelsea-manning-begins-hunger-strike-to-protest/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NEW VIDEO: celebrities, comedians, musicians, speak out against Trans-Pacific Partnership on Rock Against the TPP tour</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F9ugC4NG1Zoc&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9ugC4NG1Zoc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: September 6, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organizers of the nationwide Rock Against the TPP celebrity concert tour––which seeks to harness the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about the anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement––have released a new video featuring footage from recent stops in Seattle and Portland where the tour drew large crowds, and performances and interviews with well known artists including hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, Navajo punk band &lt;b&gt;Sihasin&lt;/b&gt;, and Danbert Nobacon of UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the new video here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/9ugC4NG1Zoc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/9ugC4NG1Zoc&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour kicked off in Denver in July and has stopped in San Diego, Seattle, and Portland. Upcoming stops include San Francisco this Friday at an event featuring revolutionary hip hop legends Dead Prez, followed by stops in Toronto, Boston, and Washington, DC. High profile participants in the tour have included Rage Against the Machine / Prophets of Rage guitarist Tom Morello, popular punk band Anti-Flag, golden globe nominated actress Evangeline Lilly, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Artists have a very special place because we have a platform we can voice the struggle. We can voice the people that dedicate their lives to the struggle. We can voice the people that’s on the front lines,” &lt;b&gt;says hip hop legend Talib Kweli during his performance.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As indigenous people, we’re kind of like the canaries in the coal mine. When there is environmental destruction, when there are corporations that are coming after our natural resources, as indigenous people we’re usually the ones on the front lines,” &lt;b&gt;Jeneda Benally of the Navajo punk band Sihasin explains in her interview. Her brother, Clayson Benally, added,&lt;/b&gt; “When you give corporations total authority and power to change laws, that’s going too far. When they first come to strip away our rights, who’s next?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is a corporate protection agreement that increases the rights of corporations and supersedes existing laws in nations that bind themselves to the contract,” &lt;b&gt;says Hawaiian slack-guitar legend Makana in the video,&lt;/b&gt; “it basically gives corporations a free pass to do whatever they want.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are more willing to listen to a musician or a comedian or a poet because they appreciate other elements. They appreciate laughter, they appreciate the music, they appreciate how something is written,” &lt;b&gt;said comedian Hari Kondabolu,&lt;/b&gt; “So if you’re somebody who’s already on board, it’s inspiring, right? People say you’re preaching to the choir, but sometimes the choir needs that. And then for folks who aren’t in the movement, who don’t see a lot of this stuff, to be in that space and actually question themselves in a way that they’re not being yelled at is another way to get the message.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s basically just a money grab,&amp;rdquo; &lt;b&gt;said Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba, &lt;/b&gt;&amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s transferring wealth from the taxpayers to corporations who are not even in the same country.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety. The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour is organized by digital rights group Fight for the Future and Firebrand Records, the social justice fueled record label from Tom Morello and Ryan Harvey. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 11:45:32 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-06-new-video-celebrities-comedians-musicians/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-06-new-video-celebrities-comedians-musicians/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” celebrity concert tour comes to San Francisco to protest Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, August 29, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Hip hop icons Dead Prez, actress Evangeline Lilly, punk legend Jello Biafra, Grammy winners La Santa Cecilia, and others to play free concert at Regency Ballroom on Friday, September 9th to protest anti-democratic TPP deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, CA––On Friday, September 9th, as part of the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, prominent musicians will lead the charge in mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP), the unpopular and anti-democratic deal that has been a contentious issue in the 2016 election. The tour, which is the largest mobilization against the TPP in U.S. history, comes to Regency Ballroom from 6pm - 11pm for a FREE event featuring legendary hip hop duo &lt;b&gt;Dead Prez&lt;/b&gt;, actress Evangeline Lilly &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt; punk icon Jello Biafra, Grammy winning latin-alternative band &lt;b&gt;La Santa Cecilia&lt;/b&gt;, riot-grrrl cellist Bonfire Madigan, and &lt;b&gt;Jeff Rosenstock&lt;/b&gt; of popular ska band Bomb the Music Industry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more details and a full lineup here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concert will be followed by a teach-in on “How to Fight the TPP” on Saturday, Sep 10th from 1pm - 3pm at 1999 Bryant Street, hosted by experts from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by digital rights group &lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt; in partnership with legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave) and riot-folk singer &lt;b&gt;Ryan Harvey&lt;/b&gt;’s record label Firebrand Records  previous stops on the tour have featured high-profile participants including &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, legendary punk band Anti-Flag, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Adult Swim comedian &lt;b&gt;Eric Andre&lt;/b&gt;, and ANTI records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The roadshow has already drawn large crowds in Denver, San Diego, Seattle, and Portland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Trans-Pacific Partnership is not about ‘free trade,’ it’s about corruption,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, &lt;/b&gt;“we’re harnessing the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about this corporate power grab and stop it in its tracks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety. The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers. Organizers plan to announce additional dates to the tour soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional performers at the September 9th event include SF indie rock darlings Built for the Sea, Taina Asili, Ryan Harvey, Evan Greer, bell’s roar, and local hip hop emcee Raw-G.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.xkq7oohiw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE PHOTOS AND VIDEO AVAILABLE FOR USE BY PRESS HERE.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with Artists or Organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 09:34:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-30-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-30-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: Rock Against the TPP Celebrity Concert Tour Draws Large Crowds in Seattle and Portland to Protest Trans-Pacific Partnership</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/669e83a68d95c6da5a94a906eb1d87a4/tumblr_inline_ocd3s1AtzY1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, August 23, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Hari Kondabolu, member of Chumbawamba among participants, comedian Eric Andre makes surprise appearance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the White House readies a final desperate push for the unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, large crowds turned out for &lt;b&gt;“Rock Against the TPP”&lt;/b&gt; events in Seattle and Portland over the weekend as part of a nationwide protest tour featuring high profile celebrities including actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu, &lt;/b&gt;and punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;. TV’s Adult Swim comedian &lt;b&gt;Eric Andre&lt;/b&gt; made a surprise appearance at the Seattle event at Showbox SoDo, while the outdoor Portland event featured a street march with an inflatable TPP “death star.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of the events available for use by press here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Short VIDEO clips are available at the bottom of this post, professional video coming soon.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both events also featured teach-ins hosted by Golden Globe nominated actress Evangeline Lilly (Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), and a panel of local experts. The Northwest dates follow previous successful tour stops in Denver and San Diego.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, United Steelworkers. The Northwest events were organized with support from the Washington Fair Trade Coalition and Oregon Fair Trade Campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the large concert events and teach-ins, the tour has brought creative protests directly to lawmakers s by flying a 25 foot blimp over Congressional offices along the tour route. So far the blimp has been sited outside the offices of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-01-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rep Scott Peters’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; office in San Diego and&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-15-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25-foot/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rep Ami Bera’s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; office in Sacramento.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour stops next in San Francisco on September 9th at Regency Ballroom with an event featuring punk legend Jello Biafra (Dead Kennedys), Grammy winning latin alternative band La Santa Cecilia, and riot-grrrl cello legend Bonfire Madigan. Additional tour dates are to be announced. For more information see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;VIDEO CLIPS BELOW. Professional video coming soon. These clips are available for use by press. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crowd chanting “Hell No TPP” at Rock Against the TPP Seattle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FiupPQ6yv9qk&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iupPQ6yv9qk?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Downtown Boys at Rock Against the TPP Portland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F3Wq8v15dIiY&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Wq8v15dIiY?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taina Asili at Rock Against the TPP in Seattle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F2ZdP5L43Nh0&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2ZdP5L43Nh0?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crowd chanting at Rock Against the TPP Portland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2Fn4Ws9PfpNg4&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/n4Ws9PfpNg4?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Navajo Nation band Sihasin performs an honor song for volunteers and artists:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FFgtw89AXnLc&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fgtw89AXnLc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 08:33:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-23-photos-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity-concert/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-23-photos-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity-concert/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Anti-TPP activists are flying a 25 foot blimp outside Representative Ami Bera’s Office protesting his support for unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/47aaa5a77e95978ae824bb466f99f1ee/tumblr_inline_obyl0kgyvE1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 15, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, press@fightforthefuture.org, 978-852-6457&lt;br/&gt;Contact on the ground: Tim Ellis, 773-458-0283&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bera faces backlash after recent comments in support of TPP. Activists fly blimp as part of awareness raising nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” tour featuring celebrities and musicians&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;SACRAMENTO, CA––8:00am PST: Activists involved with the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; celebrity concert tour are now taking their message directly to local lawmakers, flying a 25’ inflatable blimp outside Representative Ami Bera’s office at 8950 Cal Center Drive, Sacramento, CA, protesting the Congressman’s recent statements in support of the unpopular and anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more PHOTOS and VIDEO of the blimp at the bottom of this post.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activists will remain outside the office with the blimp until 11:00am PST, ensuring that it’s visible to Congressional staff as they arrive for work this morning. They will be available for interviews about the action and the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ami Bera turned his back on constituents when he voted to fast track the TPP.  We’re hoping a 25-foot blimp flying right outside his office makes it clear to him that supporting the TPP is betraying his constituents,&amp;rdquo; &lt;b&gt;said Robert Longer of CWA Local 9421.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In January, Rep. Bera failed to secure the endorsement of the local Democratic Party for his re-election to Congress, in large part due to continued constituent anger over his 2015 vote in favor of “fast track” legislation that will allow the TPP to circumvent ordinary congressional review, amendment and debate procedures.  He is among a small minority of congressional Democrats not publicly opposed to the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is a back-room deal designed to rig the global economy even further in favor of corporate elites instead of working families,”&lt;b&gt; said Fabrizio Sasso, Executive Director of the Sacramento Central Labor Council.&lt;/b&gt; “Congress members who think they can side with Wall Street over their constituents on the TPP are going to be in for a rude awakening.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airborne protest is part of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, a nationwide series of large-scale concert, protest, and teach-in events featuring high profile musicians and celebrities like T&lt;b&gt;om Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Rage Against the Machine) Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu,&lt;/b&gt; popular punk band Anti-Flag, Jello Biafra of the &lt;b&gt;Dead Kennedys&lt;/b&gt;, and Danbert Nobacon of &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;. The goal of the tour is to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular and anti-democratic “trade deal” that has been a contentious issue in the Presidential election and at both of the recent political conventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello’s new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See photos and video from the tour kick-off event &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour stopped in San Diego earlier this month, where activists &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-01-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/&#39;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;flew the same blimp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; outside Rep Scott Peters’ office. The tour has upcoming stops in Seattle, Portland, and San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: press@fightforthefuture.org for more info.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D0JdJS8LBkto%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0JdJS8LBkto?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/db7443bb5efd6479b1259f143cd96c92/tumblr_inline_obyl1nuxjo1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 12:14:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-15-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25-foot/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-15-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25-foot/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UPDATE: Celebrities Join Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Concert Tour, Raise Awareness About Toxic Trade Deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Ftime_continue%3D1%26v%3DkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, August 11, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Actress Evangeline Lilly, guitarist Tom Morello, hip hop icon Talib Kweli, punk band Anti-Flag, Dead Kennedys singer Jello Biafra, comedian Hari Kondabolu, and Others Participate in Free Concert and Teach-in Series to Protest the Trans-Pacific Partnership&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next week, August 19th-20th, as part of the nationwide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tour, prominent musicians, actors, comedians and celebrities will lead the charge in mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP). The tour, which is the largest mobilization against the TPP in U.S. history, is comprised of a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests, in an effort to educate the public about the unpopular “trade” deal that has been a hot topic in the presidential election. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lineups at each stop vary, with high-profile participants including Rage Against the Machine guitarist&lt;b&gt; Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt;, Dead Kennedys founder &lt;b&gt;Jello Biafra,&lt;/b&gt; comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, legendary punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;, Hawaiian guitar hero &lt;b&gt;Makana&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Grammy winning Latin rock band &lt;b&gt;La Santa Cecilia&lt;/b&gt;, ANTI records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;, and bilingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See details for upcoming events at the links below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 19, Seattle, WA&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 20 Portland, OR:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;September 9, San Francisco, CA:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organizers will be announcing additional dates soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.xkq7oohiw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE PHOTOS AND VIDEO HERE.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with Artists or Organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 17:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-11-update-celebrities-join-nationwide-rock-against/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-11-update-celebrities-join-nationwide-rock-against/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: Chelsea Manning supporters deliver more than 100,000 petition signatures calling for no punishment following suicide attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;958&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/6ed6abba80f4ab413149a31a1d776550/tumblr_inline_obpflofuux1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;958&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE August 10, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:christina@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;christina@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;, 202-716-1953&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future, Demand Progress, RootsAction, Bill Of Rights Defense Committee, and Care2 delivered petitions to the Secretary of the Army Wednesday morning, Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg speaks out in support of Manning&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC––This morning Chelsea Manning supporters delivered more than 115,000 petition signatures to the Secretary of the Army Eric Fanning, calling for him to drop serious new charges faced by Ms. Manning as a direct result of her attempt to take her own life on July 5th. The petitions call for the military to provide Chelsea with adequate and humane treatment for both her gender dysphoria and her suicide attempt.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more photos of the petition delivery below.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On a press call following the delivery, Chelsea’s attorney at the ACLU, Chase Strangio, said:&lt;/b&gt; “Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s access to mental health care has been inconsistent. It is an ongoing concern of her attorneys and supporters that she is not getting adequate mental health care, particularly in light of the external forces that are destabilizing her mental health, like the service of these administrative charges against her and the ongoing investigation of those charges. It seems like the government is doing everything in their power to make her physical and mental condition worsen. Punishment for these charges could not only result in significant punishment, including indefinite solitary confinement, but also loss of access to the very things that connect Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s voice with the world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg, said,&lt;/b&gt; “No harm has resulted from Chelsea Manning&amp;rsquo;s disclosures. Not giving her the proper medical treatment and then adding on these charges for her suicide attempt would seem designed to break her down as a human being. These charges appear to me to be sadistic and outrageous.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms. Manning attempted to take her own life in July after years of mistreatment in prison, and now the U.S. government is threatening to punish her further with serious &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;new charges&lt;/a&gt; directly related to her suicide attempt, which could lead to her being placed in indefinite solitary confinement, among other consequences. The 115,000 petition signatures came from petitions launched by grassroots activist groups supporting Chelsea: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://act.demandprogress.org/sign/drop-the-admin-charges-against-chelsea-manning-now/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Demand Progress&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://act.rootsaction.org/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=12415&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RootsAction&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://org.salsalabs.com/o/498/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=20166&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bill of Rights Defense Committee&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thepetitionsite.com/766/997/768/tell-the-army-not-to-put-chelsea-manning-into-solitary-confinement-for-attempting-suicide/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Care2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, a similar petition effort helped &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/aug/18/chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-petition-drop-charges&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;draw attention&lt;/a&gt; to Chelsea’s situation when she faced solitary confinement for minor prison “infractions” including possession of an expired tube of toothpaste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The photos below are available for use by press, please credit: &amp;ldquo;Courtesy Demand Progress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;4000&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2992&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/d8d97829e6ed145e7f699ac8e380687f/tumblr_inline_obpflkuYBr1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4000&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2992&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;958&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1280&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/98cf85e3363491bee7cad05db84d0395/tumblr_inline_obpfjl8Wwa1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;958&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1280&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 14:18:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-10-photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-10-photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PRESS CALL WEDNESDAY: Daniel Ellsberg Joins Chelsea Manning Attorney and Supporters to Call for No Punishment for Her Suicide Attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Media Advisory For August 10, 2016&lt;b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:christina@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;christina@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;, 202-716-1953&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future, Demand Progress, RootsAction, and Care2 will deliver 100,000+ petition signatures to Secretary of the Army on Wednesday&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC––This Wednesday, August 10, Chelsea Manning supporters will host a press conference by phone at 12:00 noon EST on the charges faced by Chelsea Manning in connection to her suicide attempt and efforts being made by supporters demanding that Secretary of the Army Eric Fanning drop the charges against Ms. Manning, and provide her with adequate treatment for both her gender dysphoria and her suicide attempt.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The press call will follow the delivery of more than 115,000 petition signatures to the Secretary of the Army and will feature Chelsea’s attorney at the ACLU, &lt;b&gt;Chase Strangio&lt;/b&gt;, Pentagon Papers whistleblower &lt;b&gt;Daniel Ellsberg&lt;/b&gt;, Fight for the Future’s campaign director, &lt;b&gt;Evan Greer&lt;/b&gt;, who speaks to Chelsea on the phone regularly, and &lt;b&gt;David Segal&lt;/b&gt;, executive director of Demand Progress, who assisted with the physical delivery of the petitions to the Secretary of the Army.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;To receive call-in details, RSVP to: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:christina@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;christina@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms. Manning attempted to take her own life after years of mistreatment in prison, and now the U.S. government is threatening to punish her further with serious &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;new charges&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; directly related to her suicide attempt in July, which could lead to her being placed in indefinite solitary confinement, among other consequences. Signatures come from petitions launched by grassroots activist groups supporting Chelsea: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://act.demandprogress.org/sign/drop-the-admin-charges-against-chelsea-manning-now/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Demand Progress&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://act.rootsaction.org/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=12415&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RootsAction&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thepetitionsite.com/766/997/768/tell-the-army-not-to-put-chelsea-manning-into-solitary-confinement-for-attempting-suicide/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Care2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, a similar petition effort helped &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/aug/18/chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-petition-drop-charges&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;draw attention&lt;/a&gt; to Chelsea’s situation when she faced solitary confinement for minor prison “infractions” including possession of an expired tube of toothpaste. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chelsea Manning is a human being who deserves to be treated with basic dignity and respect,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“The U.S. government’s treatment of her will be remembered as one of the most shameful abuses of power in our nation’s history. Everyone who cares about human rights should be speaking out against this cruelty and injustice right now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Adding additional punishment on top of Chelsea Manning&amp;rsquo;s already unjust sentence, and threatening her with indefinite solitary confinement for attempting to take her own life, is an egregious miscarriage of justice,&amp;rdquo; &lt;b&gt;said Kate Kizer, campaigner at Demand Progress.&lt;/b&gt; &amp;ldquo;The government&amp;rsquo;s inhumane reaction to Ms. Manning&amp;rsquo;s attempted suicide is part of an ongoing pattern of mistreatment that appears to be an attempt to silence Chelsea’s important voice.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 09:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-09-press-call-wednesday-daniel-ellsberg-joins/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-09-press-call-wednesday-daniel-ellsberg-joins/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Celebrity Concert Tour to Comes to Portland</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/08ff1a01296520d234704a1bc1143c77/tumblr_inline_obcj6jENrd1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 3, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:evangreer@gmail.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;evangreer@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Actress Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Hari Kondabolu, Makana, and more will lead free concert and teach-in to protest and raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership  &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portland, OR –Well known musicians, comedians, and celebrities will gather for a free concert event at Director Park on Saturday, August 20th from 5pm - 10pm. The lineup includes Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, popular punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag,&lt;/b&gt; Hawaiian slack-key guitar legend &lt;b&gt;Makana&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bilingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The free event is part of the nationwide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tour, a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular, anti-democratic “trade” deal that has been a hot topic in the presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and details for the Portland stop here: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS &amp;amp; VIDEO for use by press here:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and Oregon Fair Trade Campaign. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN: &lt;/b&gt;Saturday, August 20&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; Free, festival-style concert featuring high profile performers and speakers from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP. Food trucks. Beer garden. Kids games. 5:00pm - 10:00pm. Evangeline Lilly and TPP experts will host a free teach-in the following day, Sunday, August 21, at First Unitarian Church at 1:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; Evangeline Lilly, Hari Kondabolu, Anti-Flag (acoustic), Makana, Downtown Boys, Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba, Son of Nun, Ryan Harvey, bell’s roar, Taina Asili, Naima Penniman of Climbing Poetree, Evan Greer, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt; Director Park, 815 SW Park Ave, Portland, OR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 14:30:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>August 19: Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Celebrity Concert Tour to Comes to Seattle</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/08ff1a01296520d234704a1bc1143c77/tumblr_inline_obcjh8f8LU1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 3, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:evangreer@gmail.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;evangreer@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Hari Kondabolu, Makana, and more will lead free concert and teach-in to protest and raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership  &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seattle, WA – Internationally acclaimed hip-hop artist &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt; will perform with a full live band at a free concert at Showbox SoDo in Seattle on August 19th from 6pm - 11:30pm, as part of the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular, anti-democratic “trade” deal that has been a hot topic in the presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other high profile participants in the August 19th event include Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, comedian&lt;b&gt; Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, popular punk band Anti-Flag, Hawaiian slack-key guitar legend &lt;b&gt;Makana&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Sierra Club executive director &lt;b&gt;Michael Brune&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bilingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and details for the Seattle stop here: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;PHOTOS &amp;amp; VIDEO for use by press available &lt;/b&gt;here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.7qnmd3gmw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.7qnmd3gmw&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and Washington Fair Trade Campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN: &lt;/b&gt;Friday, August 19&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; The day will kick off at 5pm with a teach-in and training hosted by Evangeline Lilly, followed by the Rock Against the TPP concert from 6pm to 11:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag (acoustic), Makana, Downtown Boys, Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba, Son of Nun, Ryan Harvey, bell’s roar, Taina Asili, Evan Greer, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE: &lt;/b&gt;Showbox SoDo, 1700 1st Ave S, Seattle, WA (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/The+Showbox/@47.6085655,-122.3415304,17z/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Map&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 14:22:18 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-august-19-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-august-19-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

